( CAMERA CLICKING )
Am I staring ?
A little .
RUBY : Sorry .
You just have such beautiful skin .
I 'm Ruby , by the way .
Do you have a name , or you want me to guess ?
- Jesse . - Jesse .
And you just got to LA , Jesse ?
How did you know ?
You 've got that look .
Oh , don 't worry , honey .
That whole deer-in-the-headlights thing is exactly what they want .
Here . Let me help you with that .
Are you a model ?
No , I do makeup .
So , where are you staying ?
At a motel in Pasadena .
By yourself ?
Mmm-hmm .
What do your parents think about that ?
They don 't really .
Don 't think , orjust don 't care ?
They 're not around anymore .
I 'm sorry .
Hey , you wanna go somewhere ?
Where ?
A party .
What kind of party ?
The fun kind .
( ROCK MUSIC PLAYING )
( INAUDIBLE )
God , I love this color on me .
RUBY : Red Rum .
What ?
That 's what it 's called .
They say women are more likely to buy a lipstick
if it 's named after food or sex .
( TOILET FLUSHING )
Just think about it .
Black Honey .
Plum Passion .
Peachy Keen .
Pink Pussy .
( RUBY LAUGHS )
What about you , Sarah , what would your lipstick be called ?
Fuck Off .
RUBY : Apt .
What about you ?
What about me ?
Are you food
or are you sex ?
She 's dessert because she 's so sweet .
Hmm .
Shouldn 't we get back to the party ?
Don 't talk .
Still .
( RUBY LAUGHS )
So what do we think ?
I think that | wish I had your hair .
Is this your natural color ?
You are just so beautiful . Don 't you think that she 's just perfect ?
Is that your real nose ?
JESSE : Yeah .
God , life is so unfair .
Gigi just got out of the body shop . She 's still a little sensitive .
You had work done ?
You say that like it 's a bad thing .
Sweet , plastics is just good grooming .
Imagine going a year without brushing your teeth .
| go to this guy in Beverly Hills .
RUBY : Andrew . GIGI : Dr. Andrew .
- She is in love with him . - GIGI : ( CHUCKLES ) Of course I love him .
Look at me .
He calls me The Bionic Woman .
Is that a compliment ?
( SARAH SNICKERS )
I hear your parents are dead .
That must be really hard for you .
Do you have other family ?
No .
GIGI : No one at all ?
You must have a boyfriend .
( JESSE STAMMERS )
All she really wants to know is , who are you fucking ?
Sorry ?
What ?
Isn 't that what everyone wants to know ?
A pretty new girl walks into a room , everyone 's head turns .
looks her up and down , wondering ,
" Who is she fucking ?
" Who could she fuck ?
" And how high can she climb , and is it higher than me ? "
I don 't ... ldon 't know .
I just got to town , so I don 't know anybody here .
Right . But you 've slept with men before .
You do sleep with men , don 't you ?
All the time .
I think I will get back to the party .
Someone said there was gonna be a show .
RUBY : Jesse , are you coming ?
( DOOR CLOSING )
( ELECTRONIC MUSIC PLAYING )
ROBERTA : Who did you say shot these ? A boyfriend ?
Not really .
Not really or no ?
No .
It was just some guy , he found me online .
Be careful with that .
You 're very fit .
Thank you .
You 're also very young .
I think you 're perfect .
I would never say you 're fat .
But that doesn 't mean that someone else won 't .
Understand ?
I see 20 or 30 girls come in here every day .
Mostly from small towns with big dreams
because some guy named Chad in the food court told them
they were beautiful enough to be a model .
And they 're all good .
You ...
You 're going to be great .
Some girls crack under the pressure , but if you do okay ,
then we are off to New York .
You 'll work with all the top designers .
International success .
So the ﬁrst thing we need to do
is get you some pictures that are a little less amateur hour ,
no offence .
Jack MacArthur is in town . Do you know him ?
No .
Get to know him .
I had to pull some strings , but I sent him your Polaroids ,
and he has agreed to do a test with you .
How does that sound ?
It sounds great .
It sounds ...
Sounds good .
Well , there 's just a teensy bit of papenNork .
I 'll need a copy of your driver 's license and a voided check ,
and I can take those right now .
When did you graduate from high school ?
I 'm actually still kind of working on it .
I need a parental consent form .
You can go .
Parental consent form .
Just one signature there for parental consent .
One little signature and we 're off .
When someone asks , I want you to say you are 19 .
Always 19 .
Eighteen is too on the nose .
No one 's going to believe that .
Honey .
People believe what they are told .
- Hi . DEAN : - Hi .
- I have ... - I bought you flowers , but ...
- ( CHUCKLES ) Oh . Sorry . You go . - No , you first .
I was just gonna say I signed with that agency .
That 's great news . Congratulations .
Thanks .
Hey , did they say anything about my pictures ?
Didn 't come up .
Cool , that 's cool .
Come on .
Don 't forget me when you 're all famous now .
( JESSE CHUCKLES )
In Georgia , the sky is also this big .
Makes being a person down on Earth feel really small .
You could feel small here , too .
Do you ?
Sometimes .
When I was a kid ,
I would sneak out onto the roof at night .
I thought the moon looked like a big round eye .
And I would look up and I 'd say ,
" Do you see me ? "
I would stay out there for hours .
Sometimes I 'd fall asleep just dreaming .
About what ?
What I would be .
What was that ?
I could never figure it out .
I can 't sing. I can 't dance .
I can 't write . ( CHUCKLES )
No real talent .
But I 'm pretty ,
and I can make money off pretty .
So ...
I think you 're probably good at a lot of things .
You can 't tell .
We just met .
We didn 't just meet .
We met the other day .
Trust me .
I can tell .
They want me to lie .
Who wants you to lie ?
The agency .
They want me to say I 'm 19 .
How old are you ?
Sixteen last month .
You know , I think I left the stove on at home .
Stop .
( DEAN SIGHS )
DEAN : Listen. I think
you ought to do what you think is right .
I should go .
- Bye . DEAN : - Bye .
Thank you .
( SIGHS )
DEAN : Jesse .
Do you wanna go out again ?
Yeah . That ...
That 'd be cool .
( SWITCHES CLICKING )
( GASPING )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
- ( LOUD THUD ) - ( SCREAMS )
( SIREN WAILING )
( BANGING )
- HANK : Yeah ? - Something 's in my room .
What do you mean , something 's in your room ?
I saw something in my room .
HANK : Are you high ?
What are you doing ?
Calling the police .
Whoa , whoa , whoa ...
Relax , okay ?
Mikey .
MIKEY : Yeah ?
This lady has an unwanted guest .
212 .
All right , asshole . Party 's over .
Open up .
Give me the key .
( LOCK RATTLING )
( GRUNTS )
Mikey , Open the door .
( SWITCH CLICKING )
Mikey .
The fuck ?
You 're paying for this .
I didn 't do it .
- You fucking kids are all the fucking same . - ( GASPS )
lwlll find you .
Got it ?
There 's your visitor .
( SNARLING )
( CAMERA CLICKING )
( INAUDIBLE )
You 're done .
Let 's go show him .
Jack ?
Ready , ready .
Take off your shoes .
All right , everybody .
Thank you for your work .
It 's gonna be a closed set .
Idon 't mind staying . It 's not a problem .
We 're good .
( DOOR CLOSES )
Take off your clothes .
Is there a problem ?
All of it .
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
Turn around .
( OPENS CASE )
( INAUDIBLE )
Jesse .
You 're still here ?
How did it go ?
It went good .
It was great actually .
Did he say anything ?
My agency said if the pictures turned out good ,
he might consider them for an editorial .
Do you think he would ?
I think he makes a lot of promises to young girls .
I should go , before my meter runs out .
I don 't think you should be alone with him .
He seemed fine to me .
That 's not what I 'm saying , Jesse .
I 'm not as helpless as I look .
( LAUGHING )
Will you promise me something ?
Will you call me if you need anything ?
Night or day . Doesn 't matter .
Give me your phone .
It 's good to have good girls around .
- ( CAMERA CLICKS ) - ( CHUCKLES )
You promise you 'll call ?
I promise .
Thank you for the makeup today .
RUBY : Sorry I 'm late .
WAITRESS : Would you like to hear the specials ?
- Sure . - ( SCOFFS ) You 're not gonna eat it .
But they work so hard to memorize them .
WAITRESS : Today we have a loaded baked potato with a side of broccoli ,
a pan-seared halibut served with rice and a fruit cup ,
and a steak sandwich that comes with fries .
If I don 't want fries , could I substitute the fruit cup ?
WAITRESS : If you just want the fruit , you 'll have to order the fruit bowl .
How about we just have three coffees and a fruit cup ?
How was the shoot ?
Jesse was there .
Who ?
Oh , yeah , her .
Why ?
RUBY : Jack was shooting her .
What ?
She 's been in town for , like , a minute .
They brought her in for a test .
Jack doesn 't test new models .
RUBY : Well , he does now .
Apparently , they think she is gonna be this giant star .
Jack shoots me all the time .
That 's not gonna last .
GIGI : What 's that supposed to mean ?
SARAH : It means your expiration date is almost due .
Who wants sour milk when you can get fresh meat ?
Right .
Sarah , these girls come and go all the time .
She 's not special yet .
Mmm ...
But you have to admit , there is something about her .
Like what ?
She 's young , and she 's thin .
RUBY : No , it 's more than that .
She has that
thing .
( CHUCKLES )
( WOMAN CHATI 'ERING INDISTINCTLY )
( MODEL WALKING )
ASSISTANT 1 : Thank you .
CASTER : Erin .
So the same . Straight back .
ASSISTANT 1 : This way , ladies .
CASTER : So do straight back between the pillars , and then right back here .
Okay . Thank you very much .
Next .
Robert , you remember Sarah ?
( ASSISTANT 1 WHISPERING )
Oh .
CASTER : Let 's just see the walk .
Should I go again ?
CASTER : No , thank you , that will be all .
Could you come forward , please ?
This is Jesse .
Where 's your card ?
I don 't have one yet .
CASTER : Jesse 's new in town ,
but she 'sjust been signed by Roberta Hoffmann .
How old are you ?
Nineteen .
ROBERT : Any runway experience ?
Not really .
CASTER : Okay , let 's see the walk , dear .
ASSISTANT 1 : Thank you . We 'll take her to measurements .
Thank you .
ASSISTANT 2 : Lift up .
( CLEARS THROAT )
( GASPS )
( DOOR CLOSES IN THE DISTANCE )
( GLASS CRUNCHING )
- You should really fix this . - SARAH : I don 't wanna ﬁx it .
I thought you did great .
Honest .
Don 't do that .
Pretend that you don 't know .
People see you .
They notice .
Do you know how lucky you are ?
I 'm a ghost .
What 's it feel like ?
What do you mean ?
SARAH : To walk into a room ,
and it 's like in the middle of winter ,
you 're the sun .
It 's everything .
Owl
( JESSE BREATHING HEAVILY )
- Oh , shit . - SARAH : Let me see .
( GRUNTS )
Stop ! Stop !
( JESSE CONTINUES BREATHING HEAVILY )
( MACHINE WHIRRING )
( WHIRRING STOPS )
Sorry , I 'm late .
MORTICIAN : Hey . No problem .
( DOOR CLOSES )
( PANTING )
( SCREAMING )
( KNOCKING ON DOOR )
( KNOCKING CONTINUES )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
DEAN : Are you the manager ?
Depends who 's asking .
DEAN : My friend says she owes you some money .
Room 212 .
Oh , the wildcat .
That 's some real hard candy .
You know what I mean ?
I beg your pardon ?
- What , are you a Mormon ? - DEAN : No , sir .
- Are you with the DPH ? - No .
'Cause we passed our last inspection .
I can show you the papennrork if you want .
She said she owes you for the damages .
HANK : I should charge her for emotional distress .
You know how long it took to get that thing out of here ?
Well , I don 't think she should have to pay .
- That so ? - Yeah . I mean , technically it wasn 't her fault .
Not her fault ?
Who do you think left the sliding door open ?
- Yeah , but I don 't see how that makes ... - Was it you ?
- No . - Sure as hell wasn 't me .
How much ?
HANK : New door plus labor .
At least 100 .
Or was it two ?
- l have 140 in cash . - Sold .
( DOOR SLAMS )
- ls there a pharmacy around here ? - HANK : Why ?
She send you out for tampons , too ?
You know , you 've got a real attitude problem , you know that ?
I 'm just being friendly .
I just wanna make sure you 're getting something out of this deal .
'Cause if you 're not ,
got plenty of other girls here .
Take a peek in Room 214 if you get a chance .
Rented it this week to a girl from Sandusky , Ohio .
Runaway .
Thirteen years old .
Real Lolita shit .
Room 214 .
Gotta be seen .
( JESSE GROANING )
Jesse ?
What are you doing here ?
They told me to wait .
For what ?
For makeup .
You 're in the show ?
Yeah .
This show ?
Yes .
That 's my chair .
Well .
You certainly move fast .
What do you mean ?
You must be fucking him .
Sarno doesn 't let just anyone walk his collection .
I don 't think I 'm his type .
GIGI : Why not ?
You 're very masculine .
I bet they made you do the casting .
I didn 't have to .
I just come in , choose what I wanna wear .
But I 'm not sure about the makeup this year .
Yeah .
Well , flattery will get you everywhere .
You wanna know what I had done , don 't you ?
Well , I thought I 'd get more work if I went down a cup size .
So I look like a hanger . You know ?
But then my surgeon , Dr. Andrew ,
he pointed out a lot of other problems with my body .
So I had them shave my jaw , I had a slight eyebrow lift ,
new nose , cheeks , inner and outer lipo ,
oh , and they pinned my ears .
Why ?
So I could wear a ponytail .
Didn 't it hurt ?
Anything worth having hurts a little .
Besides , nobody likes the way they look .
I do .
( GIGI SCOFFS )
ASSISTANT : Are you Jesse ?
Mmm-hmm .
They wanna see you .
I already had my fitting .
I 'm just the messenger .
You .
I 've decided you 're gonna close the show .
( CAMERAS CLICKING )
ROBERT : " ... pry through the portage of the head ... "
- Hi . - " ... like a brass cannon . "
lwant you to meet my friend . This is Dean .
Hi .
- Your name 's Bean ? - NO , Dean .
- Dean ? - Dean , yeah .
ROBERT : Dean , nice to meet you . DEAN : Nice to meet you , too .
Well , come , join us . Have a drink .
Sit down .
I don 't think there 's room for two .
That 's all right , we can just sit over there .
" Now set the teeth
" and stretch the nostril wide ,
" hold hard the breath
" and bend up every spirit to his full height .
" On , on ! "
And so on and so forth .
Wow !
Did you always wanna be an actor ?
Well , performing always came naturally to me
because I 'm a creator .
All right ? I build , I make . It 's in my blood .
So whether I 'm designing a collection or creating a character ,
it 's all the same , right ?
- I went out for a ﬁlm last week . - Oh , yeah , how did it go ?
They said my face didn 't match my voice .
- Well , you can ﬁx your face . - No , don 't do that .
Why not ?
Because you can always tell when beauty is manufactured .
And if you aren 't born beautiful , you never will be .
- That 's terrible . - No , it 's true .
ldon 't think you can always tell .
Dean ,
we 're having a little debate over here , and we need your expertise .
Okay .
You know Gigi , right ?
Well , I mean , we just met .
Will you stand up so that he can take a look at you ?
Go on , stand up .
Well ?
Well , what ?
What do you think ? Do you think she is beautiful ?
I don 't know , I mean ...
Yeah , I guess she 's fine .
Yes , yes . That 's exactly the word that I was looking for .
She 's fine , right ?
You can sit down now , thanks .
Thank you , Dean .
Now look at Jesse .
Nothing fake , nothing false .
A diamond in a sea of glass .
True beauty is the highest currency we have .
Now , without it , she would be nothing .
DEAN : I think you 're wrong .
Excuse me .
I said , I think you 're wrong .
So are you gonna tell me that it 's what 's inside that counts ?
Yeah , that 's exactly what I think .
Well , I think
that if she wasn 't beautiful ,
you wouldn 't have even stopped to look .
Beauty isn 't everything . It 's the only thing .
Hey , let 's get out of here .
I wanna go .
So go .
( FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING )
What are you doing here ?
What are you ?
Is that what you want ?
You wanna be like them ?
I don 't wanna be them .
They wanna be me .
( DOOR CLOSES )
( FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING )
( DOOR OPENS )
( KNIFE CLICKS )
( GASPS )
( HANK CHUCKLES )
Wider .
( GROANS )
( GAGGING )
Wider .
( GASPS )
( DOORKNOB CLICKING )
( DOORKNOB RATTLING )
( BANGING )
( BANGING STOPS )
( DOORKNOB RATTLING IN THE DISTANCE )
( DOOR OPENING IN THE DISTANCE )
( WOMAN SCREAMING )
( WOMAN WHIMPERING )
( WOMAN SOBBING )
( WOMAN PLEADING INDISTINCTLY )
( WOMAN GRUNTING )
- ( LOUD THUD ) - ( WOMAN SCREAMS )
( WOMAN SOBBING )
( PHONE RINGING )
RUBY ON PHONE : Hello ? JESSE : ( WHISPERS ) Ruby .
- Thank God you 're awake . - RUBY : Jesse ?
JESSE : I didn 't know who to call .
RUBY : Are you okay ?
JESSE : It sounds like he 's killing her .
RUBY : What ? Who is ?
JESSE : What do I do ?
He already tried to get in .
RUBY : Can you get out ?
JESSE : I think so .
RUBY : Come here .
You 're gonna be safe .
( DOOR SLAMS )
I brought you some things .
Thanks .
You can wear this if you want .
Unless you prefer to sleep naked .
Are you going out ?
I 'm not going anywhere .
I 'm going to stay here with you .
JESSE : This house is amazing .
How long have you lived here ?
I don 't live here .
JESSE : But I thought you said this was your house .
No , I said I 'm house-sitting .
Watering the plants .
Checking the mail .
JESSE : Oh , well ...
Do you think they 'll mind that I 'm crashing ?
RUBY : You can stay here for as long as you like .
Sit .
My mom used to brush my hair after a bad day .
It 's very soothing .
Ruby ?
Just relax .
Mmm ?
Thank you .
For what ?
For being so good to me .
It 's what friends are for .
No , I mean ...
I think you 're really wonderful .
I think you 're just ...
I think you are , too .
I think you 're so beautiful .
And you have such beautiful skin .
What are you doing ?
( SHUSHING )
I thought that 's what you wanted .
NO .
Oh .
It 's not what you think .
Then what is it ?
I lied before .
I 've never been with anyone like that .
I don 't care .
Ruby .
- Stop . - ( SHUSHING )
- Stop . - I want to .
- I wanna be your first . - Stop .
- ( RUBY SHUSHING ) ( JESSE STRUGGLING )
I said stop !
( BOTH PANTING )
( DOOR CLOSES )
( DOOR LOCKING )
( SPITS )
( MOANING )
( RUBY MOANING INTENSELY )
Jesse .
What are you doing ?
JESSE : You know what my mother used to call me ?
Dangerous .
" You 're a dangerous girl . "
She was right .
I am dangerous .
I know what I look like .
And what 's wrong with that anyway ?
Women would kill to look like this .
They carve and stuff
and inject themselves .
They starve to death ,
hoping ,
praying that one day they 'll look like a second-rate version of me .
Are we having a party or something ?
( GROANS )
( GRUNTS )
( GASPS )
( GROANS )
( JESSE GASPS )
( GASPS )
( GROANING SOFTLY )
( SHOWER RUNNING )
ANNIE : My girlfriend , she hasn 't worked in months .
I mean , I keep telling her , " Girl , you need to retire . "
MAKEUP ARTIST : Right .
ANNIE : Once you hit 21 in this industry , you 're so irrelevant .
MAKEUP ARTIST : ( SCOFFS ) Try 20 .
ANNIE : ( CHUCKLES ) True . She won 't listen .
MAKEUP ARTIST : Of course she won 't .
ANNIE : No .
I mean , she 's so desperate , the other day she went uptown ,
she was trying to buy this baby seal fat from this random woman .
( SCOFFD )
What , you think that 's funny ?
No , I don 't .
( CHUCKLES )
You ever had a girl screw you out of a job ?
Yes .
So what did you do about it ?
I ate her .
ANNIE : Ew ! ( LAUGHS )
Gross .
Do I know you ?
What are you doing here ?
I 'm waiting for my friend .
I 'd like to use you for this .
Would you be okay with that ?
Annie , you 're fired !
Thank you .
ANNIE : Are you serious ?
It 's not fair .
You ... You can 't ﬁre me .
( GIGI RETCHING )
Gigi .
Can you tell us what 's so interesting ?
You 're staring in the pool .
Look in the camera .
( CONTINUES RETCHING )
( COUGHS )
( RETCHING )
( GROANING )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( RETCHING )
( GIGI BREATHING HEAVILY )
( GIGI CONTINUES RETCHING )
( GIGI CRYING )
I need to get her out of me .
( GIGI RETCHING )
( STABS )